This file encapsulates the business logic. Each service perform a specific domain task.

It can be consumed by controllers and other services. Services should never directly interact
with the database.

In context of our software, services induce tenant-level rules like tenant quotas, user limits, and
data visibility) and orchestrates interactions across repositories

For example:
- TenantService = Registers a new tenant with default settings
- AuthService = Handles tenant-aware user authentication