    The purpose of this directory is to handle incoming HTTP requests and map them to actions.

    In our software, we can put TenantController, UserController, and CompanyController here. They can be used to validate
    which tenant is making the request.

    Handles HTTP requests from the client and returns appropriate responses. Controllers act as the entry point to the 
    application logic, routing user actions (GET/POST/etc.) to services that handle the core business logic.

    Controller should not contain business logic! Only ocrchtestration and delegation. For example:
    - TenetController: Manages tenant registration and update tenanat settings
    - UserController: Handles login, profile updates, and role management